Finding Aid for William Haber Papers, 1918-1988
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Miscellaneous
  - Papers from the William Haber residence (Box 48)
- University Of Wisconsin Files
  - Student Notebooks And Papers (Box 48)
  - Student Notebooks And Papers (Box 49)